http://www.horses-and-horse-information.com/privacy.shtml

You are here: > Horses > Privacy Statement
Privacy Statement
General.
you do not want your personal information collected
when you visit our website.
Personal Information.
information collected, please do not submit it to
us.
If you have already submitted this information and
would like for us to remove it from our records,
please contact us at the e-mail address listed at
the bottom of this Statement. We will use
reasonable efforts to delete your information from
our existing files.
When you do provide us with personal information,
we may use that information in the following ways,
will not provide that information to third
parties.
Children.
efforts to delete the child's information from our
existing files.
Other information collected automatically.
URL of the website from which you
linked or clicked to our website.
Information we may place automatically on your computer's hard drive.
allow us to tailor our website to better match your
interests and preferences.
Some of our advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP , the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed.
This is generally used for geotargeting purposes (showing California restuarant ads to someone in California, for example) or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing scrapbooking ads to someone who frequents scrapbooking sites).
With most Internet
Browsers, you can erase cookies from your computer
hard drive, block all cookies, or receive a warning
before a cookie is stored. Please refer to your
browser instructions or help screen to learn more
about these functions.
Specific to the Google Ads displayed on this site
Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads our your site. Their DART cookie enables them and their partners to serve ads to your users based on their visit to our sites and/or other sites on the Internet. Web surfers may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy
Who to contact.
If you have submitted personal information through
this website and would like that information
deleted from our records, please contact us at the
following e-mail address:
privacy@horses-and-horse-information.com.
We will use reasonable efforts to delete your
information from our existing files.
Register below to get free horse tips from:
Name:
E-Mail
Horse Tack & Riding Equipment MaintenanceTack needs to be maintained religiously. Synthetic tack can be hosed down or washed in the washing machine. It's lighter in weight, easy to care for, and less expensive than leather. Leather, needs much more care. Inspect it every time you clean it. Wash it every time you use it, and then oil the leather parts a few times a year.Browse some different types and styles of synthetic and leather horse tack available online.
Horse Education
Horse Training Teleseminar
Horse Information Topics
Horse health
Horse nutrition / feed
Horse pasture / forage
Horse care
Horse tack / equipment
Horse names (5,000)
Have your horse products or services exposed to over 27,000 of our monthly visitors.
Copyright (c) 2011. American Horse Rider & Horses and Horse Information. All rights reserved.
